three things I like about the gym
Reaper's wrist straps other support they
provide my wrist they don't take away my
mobility and the thumb Loop allows me to
get a nice secure fit I've been using
these wrist straps for quite some time
and I'm pretty excited to break them
down for y'all
what's up everybody it's Jake back in
the barbing garage gym with another
review ready to go for y'all this time
I've got a pair of wrist wraps from gym
Reapers now in this video I'm gonna tell
you everything you need to know about
these wraps from the price and the
features some pros and cons and of
course who should or maybe should not
buy these but before I get going with
all that I gotta let you know we've
reviewed a lot of wrist wraps on
barbin.com so if you want to browse our
best list well all you got to do is
search bar Bend best wrist straps and
you can find out for yourself which ones
that we like the best
okay so I want to talk about what I like
about these wrist straps and I really
want to kick this off with the amount of
support and stability they provide your
wrist so coming from somebody who had a
pretty significant wrist injury in the
past you know these definitely get the
job done in terms of providing my risk
with that proper support that I need
when I'm working out but cool thing is
they don't really take away from my
Mobility now I've also used a ton of
wrist tape in my time as well and you
know tape can sometimes hinder your
mobility and your flexibility with your
wrist and that's something that I really
haven't experienced with these wrist
straps the thumb Loop is also really
nice it's going to allow you to get you
know really snug fit when you go to get
ready to work out and they're really
good quality and they're priced for
around twenty dollars so you know
considering that price tag you know
comparing that to tape specifically you
know you're going to save a lot of money
in the long run and these are going to
last you a good amount of time
okay now that there are a few potential
cons you may experience with these wrist
straps let's talk about the width first
so these are three inches wide and that
might not be ideal for everybody who
really just wants to pinpoint this area
right here where that ligament runs
across your wrist and you know if that's
the case you probably want to consider
some thinner wrist straps now let's talk
about the fit as well yeah you can
definitely get a tight fit with these
wraps but might not be as tight as what
you can find you know you're able to get
with some wrist tape but that doesn't
always you know mean it's better right
so it's too tight you know you might cut
off your circulation that's happened to
me with tape before it doesn't really
feel good your hand kind of starts to
fall asleep so definitely keep that in
mind and then lastly is the amount of
Mobility you have with these wraps so I
personally like that I like that my
wrist can be flexed a little bit but
that's something you don't really want
you know I get that and if that's the
case then maybe you might want to
consider some stiff wraps you know Jim
Reapers actually has some which you
might want to take a look at
all right so let's talk about price
these gym Reaper's wrist straps are
available for right around 20 bucks on
the Jim Reaper's website you can also
purchase them from Amazon if you'd
rather do that now let's compare this
price to tape all right so up front tape
is you know going to be cheaper when you
go to you know your local sporting goods
store you know whatever that's
definitely going to be cheaper but in
the long run you're definitely going to
be spending more money with risk tape
you know especially because it's a one
and done kind of thing I've never seen
somebody reuse wrist tapes if you can
good for you but that's probably not
gonna happen now considering that you
know these are high quality the
longevity of them you know that's a
really good thing right here going for
these and yeah there's definitely more
expensive wrist wraps out there but that
doesn't always mean that they're better
now my opinion considering that twenty
dollars is a really fair price and these
are really good quality I gotta say I
think you're getting a really good deal
right here
[Applause]
okay so in terms of the build gym
Reapers uses a combo of polyester and
elastic for these wrist straps they're
pretty comfortable in my opinion and I
really like the thumb Loop right here
you know it's going to allow you to get
that tight fit that you want but these
are also you know technically
customizable with your support because
of the elastic so you can make them as
tight or really as Loose as you really
want but that thumb Loop is going to be
nice because it's going to prevent the
wrist strap from sliding down your arm
these are 18 inches long and three
inches wide like I said so this is
technically one size fits all but not
everybody's going to be crazy about that
three inch wide profile so definitely
keep that in mind that's something that
you know you're really not looking for
there's nine different color ways for
you to choose from so there's a lot of
variety right there for you to pick from
and kind of match your Gym gear you know
whatever you have and it's really cool
there's a lifetime warranty with these
wrist straps it's going to cover any
manufacturing defects so not any normal
wear and tear from usage but if you
notice anything wrong with the product
look that you didn't do you know just
notify Jim Reapers and they're gonna
send you some new ones
[Music]
so it's time for your favorite part of
the video the walk around portion so
let's talk about the material you know
once again this is a mix of polyester
and elastic so it stretches pretty far
you can get a nice tight fit on your
wrist but I also think it's pretty
comfortable as well too it doesn't make
my wrist itch whatsoever now I really
like this thumb Loop makes it super easy
to you know put this on your wrist and
just get a really nice tight fit so just
put that around your thumb
get this seam nice and lined up where
you want it to be I like putting them on
a little bit above my wrist right there
to give my wrist the maximum support
when I'm working out so simply position
everything where you want
wrap it around as far as you really want
it to go and then it's like Smooth
Sailing after that you're ready to get
right to working out obviously it's just
reverse process taking it off it's
velcro right here though not gonna come
loose It's Gonna Keep it you know right
where it should be on your wrist and
then afterwards you know to get it nice
and you know tightly stored like that
just simply roll it up as you would with
the burrito
so you get all the way down right here
to the velcro
and it's going to make it super easy for
you to store it in your bag or even in
your pocket if you really wanted to now
once again you know these are 18 inches
long so it's kind of a one size fits all
thing and three inches wide I mean as
you can see it was kind of wide right
here on my wrist I don't really think
it's too bulky but I kind of understand
why some people might not like that
because it definitely takes up a good
amount of you know space on your wrist
last thing right here really fast
whenever it comes to cleaning these
definitely you know just hand wash it
you don't want to throw it in with the
laundry or definitely not the dryer want
to let them air dry that way you know
none of the stitching or anything really
gets messed up or the velcro and it
doesn't you know shrink on you either
okay so let's talk about who should
purchase these wrist straps from Jim
Reapers well if you're looking for a
wrist strap it's going to provide you
with a solid amount of support and
stability while lifting without you know
sacrificing that flexibility of your
wrist I think this is a really good
option for you to consider you know once
again coming from somebody with a wrist
injury you know I definitely need that
added stability when I'm lifting yeah
it's definitely a mental thing I think
we all kind of go through that sometimes
but you know having that extra support
right here on my wrist allows me to grip
tighter you know that's definitely you
know a positive right there I also think
they're pretty comfortable so you know
if that's something you're looking for
in a wrist strap I think you should
strongly consider these they're also
going to save you money compared to risk
tape and they're high quality so if you
are in fact looking for some wrist
straps that are built to last I think
this is what you've been looking for
right here
[Music]
now when it comes to those people who
might not want to purchase these wrist
straps comes down to three different
things all right so even though it's
more expensive over time you know some
people may just prefer the feel that
tape provides them you know if that's
you you may be better off going down the
old-fashioned round not everybody is
looking for the amount of flexibility
that you get with these wrist straps and
you know if that's you you're probably
going to want to consider a stiffer
wrist strap and once again gym Reapers
has some that you might want to consider
and they're also pretty wide not
everybody is going to be crazy about
that so if they do in fact feel too
bulky on your wrist you might want to
consider a thinner option all right well
that's a wrap on today's review over the
Jim Reaper's wrist wraps I personally
love working out with these you know I
need that extra support that these
provide they definitely allow me to get
straight to my workout without any
hesitation whatsoever the thumb Loop
right here you know really makes it
possible for you to get the exact amount
of compression that you need while
lifting and plus you know that's going
to prevent the wrist wrap from sliding
down your arm or at least making it feel
like it's going to slide down your arm
they're also a budget friendly option
compared to buying tape multiple times a
year and I really like that I still have
some flexibility when I'm working out
but if you don't like that amount of
flexibility I would definitely suggest
finding yourself some stiffer wrist
straps thanks for watching y'all I hope
this video was really helpful and I was
able to answer every single question you
may have about these wrist straps as
always stay posted for my next review
but for now you should absolutely head
over to barbin.com and you can read more
about this product all you have to do is
search barbin gym Reapers wrist wrap
review you can read everything that I
talked about here today I'll see you all
next time
foreign
[Music]